For a lot of folks, your version of being an American has been dealing with simply the issue of the United States and how it treats being a citizen of this nation.
However, I want to inform you that those days are ending because we are on a planet and we've been on a planet the whole time, but we are now being really, really cognitively made aware of this.
Something I want to bring to your attention, if you did not know, is that Israel, which is the United States, just took the life and assassinated the Yemeni prime minister and its cabinet members.
Please look up Yemen and find out where Yemen is.
Yemen is also home to the Houthis.
The Houthis are a resistance group that has actively been fighting to basically stand on the side of Palestinians.
The Houthis announced today, oh, y'all want to merc our prime minister?
We gon' merc your prime minister.
What I see a lot of people saying is that Israel is America's bitch.
And I just want to bring to your attention, no, Israel is America's colony.
And basically, when you see Benjamin Netanyahu saying, nah, y'all got to do this, it's because he's saying, I'm your colony.
And if you want to really do what you want to do over here, you need to provide us with the tools to do so.
Imperialism is like having a franchise of Popeyes.
If you're going to have multiple Popeyes, you can't only give one of them the chicken sandwich.
Because the chicken sandwich is what's controlling anybody coming to the Popeyes.
So all of your franchises is going to need the chicken sandwich.
In this metaphor, the chicken sandwich is money and weapons.
And that is why everyone from Kamala Harris to Donald Trump have been complicit.
Barack Obama was dropping joints on Yemen like Funk Flex was on Hot 97.
Whether Democrats or Republicans, all have been complicit.
Because ever since World War II, the United States said it's going to be the actual global colonizer replacing Britain.
And in order to do so, it's going to have sentinels all across the world.
And Israel is one of those.
I know this is a lot to take in on a day off.
But I just want to keep y'all updated because I know so many of us get into our own main character energy in this movie.
And we need to realize that the movie is bigger than us.
And that's the only way that we're going to actually change the plot of the film.